[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Hearing Whitney sing a song say \"Don't Cry for Me,\" what goes through your mind when you hear that?", "question_tokens": ["Hearing", "Whitney", "sing", "a", "song", "say", "``", "Do", "n't", "Cry", "for", "Me", ",", "''", "what", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "when", "you", "hear", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "``", "NNP", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "''", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "INANS: Well, it causes, it triggers memories for me, pleasant memories.", "answer_tokens": ["INANS", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "causes", ",", "it", "triggers", "memories", "for", "me", ",", "pleasant", "memories", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "And you wrote this song?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "wrote", "this", "song", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I wrote this song and CeCe singing it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wrote", "this", "song", "and", "CeCe", "singing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 26 years"], "LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "As somebody who knew her really well, what is the truth about Whitney in the last 10 years, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["As", "somebody", "who", "knew", "her", "really", "well", ",", "what", "is", "the", "truth", "about", "Whitney", "in", "the", "last", "10", "years", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, the truth about Whitney, let's go back with me and family, the last 26 years of her life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "truth", "about", "Whitney", ",", "let", "'s", "go", "back", "with", "me", "and", "family", ",", "the", "last", "26", "years", "of", "her", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 10 years"], "LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Were you as shocked as other people about what happened to her, in the sense of -- was there a sense of inevitability that Whitney wouldn't lead a long life given the lifestyle that she had chosen for herself?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "as", "shocked", "as", "other", "people", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "her", ",", "in", "the", "sense", "of", "--", "was", "there", "a", "sense", "of", "inevitability", "that", "Whitney", "would", "n't", "lead", "a", "long", "life", "given", "the", "lifestyle", "that", "she", "had", "chosen", "for", "herself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "I think the shock is great because we walked through, I think a darker valley five, 10 years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "shock", "is", "great", "because", "we", "walked", "through", ",", "I", "think", "a", "darker", "valley", "five", ",", "10", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Did she find superstardom very hard to deal with?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "find", "superstardom", "very", "hard", "to", "deal", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "She tried to run away from it.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "tried", "to", "run", "away", "from", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney", "Whitney"]}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "And when you understand that reality, you don't want that, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "when", "you", "understand", "that", "reality", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "want", "that", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Aretha Franklin repeated a few people, Baby Face came in here earlier this week and told me this too, one of the big blows to Whitney was when she went to the Soul Train Awards in the early '90s and she was booed for the first time by an audience because they had had enough of Whitney.", "answer_tokens": ["Aretha", "Franklin", "repeated", "a", "few", "people", ",", "Baby", "Face", "came", "in", "here", "earlier", "this", "week", "and", "told", "me", "this", "too", ",", "one", "of", "the", "big", "blows", "to", "Whitney", "was", "when", "she", "went", "to", "the", "Soul", "Train", "Awards", "in", "the", "early", "'90s", "and", "she", "was", "booed", "for", "the", "first", "time", "by", "an", "audience", "because", "they", "had", "had", "enough", "of", "Whitney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Do you remember that time?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "that", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Yes, I remember that time.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "remember", "that", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Is she OK?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "She's good.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "I think it's important.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "``", "NNP", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "How much blame is it fair to (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "blame", "is", "it", "fair", "to", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I think I could go right back to that lyric in \"Don't Cry for Me\" where she sings, no one is to blame, my death was meant to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "could", "go", "right", "back", "to", "that", "lyric", "in", "``", "Do", "n't", "Cry", "for", "Me", "''", "where", "she", "sings", ",", "no", "one", "is", "to", "blame", ",", "my", "death", "was", "meant", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Did you ever doubt that she loved Bobby Brown?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "doubt", "that", "she", "loved", "Bobby", "Brown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "You know, you're funny.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "you", "'re", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby Brown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJS", ",", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Did you ever try to save her, perhaps on herself, when it came to the drugs?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "try", "to", "save", "her", ",", "perhaps", "on", "herself", ",", "when", "it", "came", "to", "the", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, I'll be very honest,.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "be", "very", "honest", ",", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stevie"], "LOCATION": ["Detroit", "Michigan"]}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How are you feeling about this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Not nervous at all, because when you talk about Stevie, you talk about someone that used to live around the corner from me in Detroit, Michigan, when you talk about Aretha, you're talking about Auntie Rere (ph), when you talk about these people, these are people that we were blessed to meet early on and we became family.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "nervous", "at", "all", ",", "because", "when", "you", "talk", "about", "Stevie", ",", "you", "talk", "about", "someone", "that", "used", "to", "live", "around", "the", "corner", "from", "me", "in", "Detroit", ",", "Michigan", ",", "when", "you", "talk", "about", "Aretha", ",", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "Auntie", "Rere", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "when", "you", "talk", "about", "these", "people", ",", "these", "are", "people", "that", "we", "were", "blessed", "to", "meet", "early", "on", "and", "we", "became", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffrey Osborne"]}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "When you get up to sing, what will you be thinking about when it comes to Whitney?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "get", "up", "to", "sing", ",", "what", "will", "you", "be", "thinking", "about", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "Whitney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I'll -- honestly I'll be thinking and this is -- this is full circle for me because the first day we met, she was opening for Jeffrey Osborne.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "--", "honestly", "I", "'ll", "be", "thinking", "and", "this", "is", "--", "this", "is", "full", "circle", "for", "me", "because", "the", "first", "day", "we", "met", ",", "she", "was", "opening", "for", "Jeffrey", "Osborne", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What can you tell me about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "We need to remain vigilant, always.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "need", "to", "remain", "vigilant", ",", "always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Nine times eight?", "question_tokens": ["Nine", "times", "eight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Seventy two.", "answer_tokens": ["Seventy", "two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Roger, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Roger", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "So you had that dream, too?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "had", "that", "dream", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Be honest -- and you've got to be absolutely honest with me -- did you know how good he really was?", "question_tokens": ["Be", "honest", "--", "and", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "be", "absolutely", "honest", "with", "me", "--", "did", "you", "know", "how", "good", "he", "really", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Because you played yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "played", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "I would like to say because I played myself and because I have a pretty good eye for talent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "to", "say", "because", "I", "played", "myself", "and", "because", "I", "have", "a", "pretty", "good", "eye", "for", "talent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Does he pick his nose or what happens?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "pick", "his", "nose", "or", "what", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "He's very outgoing.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "very", "outgoing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "So I mean, he is the genuine deal, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "is", "the", "genuine", "deal", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "He is, I mean, he's legitimate.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "'s", "legitimate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", ":", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What is the single biggest offer you have so far had for Jeremy Lin?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "single", "biggest", "offer", "you", "have", "so", "far", "had", "for", "Jeremy", "Lin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, I have had too many really to --.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "had", "too", "many", "really", "to", "--", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremy Lin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Just hard ready?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "hard", "ready", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "We haven't -- I'm not being vague, because what we haven't done is we really haven't vetted an offer that we have been really, really serious about to this point.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "n't", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "being", "vague", ",", "because", "what", "we", "have", "n't", "done", "is", "we", "really", "have", "n't", "vetted", "an", "offer", "that", "we", "have", "been", "really", ",", "really", "serious", "about", "to", "this", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Two million?", "question_tokens": ["Two", "million", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "That's very possible.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "very", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Higher?", "question_tokens": ["Higher", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Very possible.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "You have had higher offers?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "had", "higher", "offers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I have had offers in that range.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "had", "offers", "in", "that", "range", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "You must be enjoying this, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "enjoying", "this", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Is this the greatest moment of your career?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Do you want them to take it better?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "them", "to", "take", "it", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "No, I didn't want them to take it badly in the first place.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "want", "them", "to", "take", "it", "badly", "in", "the", "first", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Too easy, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Too", "easy", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I mean --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "That's what they call a home run, you know?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "they", "call", "a", "home", "run", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ":", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Do you know if he finds it funny?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "if", "he", "finds", "it", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well, again, I don't -- I don't go for people -- things about people they can't help.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "go", "for", "people", "--", "things", "about", "people", "they", "ca", "n't", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Do you have a moral code yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "moral", "code", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Of course I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120217pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "How would you define it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "define", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, you can't.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]